[instrumental music]
Tanner Yo-yo's a dribble.
He fakes left,
he drives right
he puts Michelle
in the popcorn machine
and he jams her right over
two feet eight inches
of towering toddler. Yes!
- My turn.
- Okay, here we go.
It's Tanner
versus Tanner
for all the marbles.
Michelle breaks
for the basket
and goes right
through my legs.
Okay, she's going
for that super-duper
highflying baby skying, junior,
junior, slammer, jammer..
Talk about serious
hang time.
Michelle scores!
[Danny laughs]
- In your face.
NBA Action.
- It's...
- Fantastic!
[John Stamos singing
"Full House" theme song]
♪ Aah aah aah aah ♪
♪ Aah ♪
♪ Whatever happened
to predictability ♪
♪ The milkman
the paper boy ♪
♪ Evenin' TV ♪
♪ Aah ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ There's a heart ♪
♪ A hand to hold on to ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ There's a face ♪
♪ Of somebody who needs you ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ When you're lost out there ♪
♪ And you're all alone ♪
♪ A light is waitin' ♪
♪ To carry you home ♪
♪ Everywhere you look ♪
♪ Dooby doo baa ba dow ♪♪
[instrumental music]
Well, the sandbox is all ready
for Michelle's playgroup.
Great, and I have prepared
a nutritious platter
of celery sticks
for her little friends.
Hmm, celery sticks,
every kid's favorite.
I remember, every Halloween
I used to head straight
to the houses that gave
out celery.
[Stephanie mumbling]
What'd she say?
She said..
Honey, take that apple
out of your mouth.
Now, what did
you say?
I said, don't pull
that apple out of my mouth.
My loose tooth is stuck!
Not anymore.
It's in this apple.
It came out!
I was jiggling it around
with my tongue for a week.
I could bend it all the way
back, but it kept hanging
by this one little, slimy,
skinny string of tooth guts.
I'm going to go put
this under my pillow
right now for the tooth fairy.
This thing is money
in the bank.
- Stephanie?
- D.J.?
Wait till you hear
what happened to me.
- My tooth came out.
- That's nothing.
- I jumped my first fence today!
- Big deal.
You didn't jump it,
your horse did.
[sighs]
So you didn't lose your tooth,
your gums did.
- I'll tell you what happened.
- No, okay?
Come on, partner.
Mosey on in here.
Don't be a baby.
You know you had fun.
That horse had
it in for me.
I tried to be nice to him.
I gave him a sugar cube.
- Jesse?
- Okay, so it was Sweet'N Low.
The point is, I was nice
to him and how does he thank me?
Bada-boom! He throws me
in the mud.
And then he laughs at me.
[laughing]
Oh, my back!
Get me a seat.
- Better?
- Yes.
Good, the next time
we go riding
I promise, I'm gonna get you
a cute little pony.
I think not. I had
a little chat with my butt.
We both decided there'll
be no more horseback riding.
[speaking in foreign language]
Jesse, that's not fair. I always
do everything that you wanna do.
- Like what?
- Like go hear your band play.
Yeah, but that's fun.
Well, I happen to think
that riding a horse is fun.
Hold on a second.
Wo-ah-ah-ah-ah!
You mean to tell me that horse
riding is more fun than music?
When was the last time
you saw Mr. Ed
play in front of 50,000
screaming fans, huh?
And did Guns N' Roses
ever win the Kentucky Derby?
Alright. If you don't wanna go
to the Smash Club tonight, fine.
Then just skip it, okay? Good.
Becky?
Jesse.
How about a nice soothing
back rub, huh?
Okay, I could really use one.
And then a little
spaceship landed.
[beeping]
Is this a...playgroup
or an oil painting?
Okay, here we go!
Great, Danny.
I'm dying out here.
Nothing to worry about.
I've got something
you kids are gonna love.
No more celery!
No more celery.
Toys!
Here you go.
And I got a pail, and a
sand-strainer and a bunch of--
Whoa, whoa! Lenny, Lenny..
Very uncool. Sand belongs
in the sandbox.
Tell you what,
Len, buddy..
how would you like to
trade-in that shovel
for a red, white
and blue woggly-do?
(Lenny)
'Yeah.'
My toy!
No, Michelle, it's not nice
to be selfish.
Oh, Joey, no, I'm sure
my sweet little Michelle
was just informing this
little sand crab here
that, that is one
of her favorite toys.
Here, Lenny, play with this.
My toy!
You wanna try
for a third toy
or do you see
a pattern developing here?
Alright, maybe she's heading
into a little selfish stage.
Hey, it happens in families.
No one knows why.
Here, Lenny,
play with this.
Joey, that's my whisk broom.
Okay, here, Lenny, but try
not to bend any bristles.
D.J....I've been thinking.
Uh-oh.
Santa Claus works
one night a year
and always gets
milk and cookies.
The tooth fairy
works every night
and all she gets is
a sack full of old teeth.
If there's a point
to this, please get to it.
The point is..
...I'm leaving the tooth fairy
milk and cookies.
Don't try to stop me..
...I've made up my mind.
End of story, case closed,
good night, and good luck.
So young and yet,
so strange.
- Hey, Deej.
- Hi, Becky.
Hey, do you think we can go
riding next week?
Sure. Deej, you were
amazing today.
When did you decide
to jump that fence?
Well, when the horse
was about halfway over.
I figured, as long
as I'm up here
I might as well go for it.
Hey, Beck, I'm glad
you're here early.
Listen, the band doesn't go
until nine, so I figured
we get a bite to eat
before we go?
Oh, great! Okay, dinner
sounds good.
But, uh, Jess,
I've been thinking
about the club.
Maybe you were right.
Of course, I was right.
What did I say?
Well, you said if I didn't feel
like going to the club
then I should just skip it.
Oh, well, when I said,
"skip it, skip"
I-I didn't mean, "don't go
to the club skip it."
I meant, you know,
"skip the argument, skip it."
Oh, I see-I see.
So you didn't really mean it
when you said
you were never
gonna go riding again?
Oh, no!
I meant that.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah.
But why don't you wanna
come to the club?
Oh, because you play
the same songs
three sets a night three nights
a week. Right, Joey?
Hey, come on, the Smash Club
is fun. Right, Joey?
Fun? It's loud.
It's smoky.
Oh, and, of course, they keep
that ladies' room immaculate!
Tell her she's wrong
about the ladies' room.
Tell him I'm right
I think I better just
stay out of the ladies room.
Joey, can you believe
that she's not going
to the Smash Club tonight?
- Becky, is that true?
- Yes.
- Well, then I believe it.
- Go wash!
(Michelle on walkie-talkie)
'Hello, Uncle Jesse.'
'It's me, Michelle Tanner.'
Somebody probably wants
to hear me sing.
Coming, Michelle.
Why do you men cling
to your antiquated
macho attitudes?
Because we're tough
and we're rugged.
Now, take a hike, toots,
so I can separate
my wash and wears
from my delicates.
Yes, can I help you,
young lady?
- A kiss, please?
- Oh!
Alright, upside-down kiss.
Upside-down kiss.
See, somebody
still loves me.
Michelle, can I talk to you?
I'm a monkey.
[mimicking a monkey]
Can I tell you my problem first?
Alright, listen to this.
My toy.
Oh, Michelle, now you
don't wanna grow up
and be selfish
like Becky?
(Jesse on walkie-talkie)
'And the next thing you know,
you won't wanna go'
'hear your boyfriend sing.'
'I don't know what's got
into Becky lately'
'but she's really starting
to get on my nerves.'
After seven, already?
I better check
that garbage disposal.
[machine whirring]
(Jesse)
'I mean, sometimes she gets
so stubborn and pig-headed..'
Excuse me.
You know, sometimes those things
pick up other people's houses!
Oh, Michelle, why can't
Becky just realize
that your Uncle Jesse
is right?
I mean, it's so simple..
It's so sim..
Hi!
Oh, you found the baby monitor,
didn't you?
Michelle, do that imitation
of me again.
I wanna talk to you, alone.
Hey, anything you
can say to me
you can say
in front of my niece.
- No, that's not true.
- You see what I'm saying?
Here, hold this.
- Becky?
- Stubborn? Pig-headed?
Well, it just so happens
that this stubborn pig-head
only goes to that
club to be with you!
Then why are we arguing?
Let's go.
No way!
If you don't wanna do
what I wanna do
why should I do
what you wanna do?
Oh, I get. This whole thing
is about revenge.
You're punishing me.
You don't wanna go to my club
'cause I don't wanna
ride your stupid horses,
is that it?
Oh, well, it just so happens
that those stupid horses
are a lot smarter
than you.
Just admit it.
Say that I'm right.
- Say I'm right.
- Okay, I'm right.
Funny.
Don't you dare walk out
that door.
Don't you dare leave
this hallway.
I'm talking to you.
Don't you dare take
that step, or that step
or that step,
or that step.
Okay, what do
you wanna say?
I just wanna tell
you that, uh
that-that this whole thing
is your fault.
- Oh-oh, my fault?
- Yeah.
Well, I disagree. But what else
is new? We always disagree.
We're completely
different people with
completely
different interests.
Fine, maybe we should
start dating other people
we have more
in common with.
Oh, so that's what you want?
It's obviously what you want.
Oh, well then fine!
This relationship is over.
- Goodbye, Jesse!
- Fine, goodbye, Rebecca!
[sighs]
[instrumental music]
[alarm clock buzzing]
Alright, it's morning!
I've been waiting all night
for this.
Stephanie, it's Saturday.
It's also tooth fairy day.
What did you do?
Whoa, baby!
You're whoa, babying about
a dollar bill?
Does this look like
Twenty dollars?
Whoa, baby!
I knew those milk
and cookies would pay off.
You nerd bomber. I ate
the milk and cookies.
You're in trouble
this Christmas.
The tooth fairy and Santa Claus
are like this.
I don't know, Jesse,
maybe you'd feel a lot better
if you just called Rebecca
and apologized.
Oh, Danny, I gotta face it.
It ain't happening, man.
We don't have one thing
in common.
- Oh, sure you do.
- What's that?
You're both crazy
about me.
Guess what?
The tooth fairy left me $20!
$20? Whoa, baby!
This isn't fair, dad.
How come the tooth fairy
never left me
that kind of cash?
Well, possibly the tooth fairy
was fumbling around in the dark
and, uh, accidentally
took the wrong bill
out of his,
or her, wallet.
Well, I certainly hope
the allowance fairy
makes the same mistake.
Alright, alright, everybody
get your pancakes here.
- Ooh!
- Pancakes, alright.
- My pancakes.
- No, no, Michelle.
Honey, those are
for everybody.
Why don't we all show Michelle
how much fun sharing can be?
- Good idea.
- Excellent idea, Joey.
Now, Michelle, watch this.
I am going to share
my pancake..
...with Joey.
Thank you, Danny,
and I am going to share
my pancake with D.J..
How thoughtful!
And I'm going to share
my pancake
with my incredibly fortunate
little sister.
You're too kind.
And I'm happy to share
with my Uncle Jesse.
Thank you very much.
And I'm going to share with
one of my three favorite nieces
Michelle. There you go.
Now, isn't sharing fun,
everybody?
(all)
Oh, yes!
I wish someone would share
their pancake with me!
Here, daddy.
Thank you, Michelle.
I'm so proud of you.
And I won't even
have to chew it.
[knock on the door]
It's Becky.
I knew she'd be back
to apologize.
- Hi, Danny.
- Hi, everyone.
Mr. Katsopolis, you left
some things at my apartment.
I assume, you'd want your
emergency blow dryer back.
And your emergency
styling spray.
Oh, no, I think you made a
mistake, this must be yours.
It's for "hard
to manage hair."
Oh, no, no, this must be yours.
It's for vain and pompous hair.
Are you guys having a fight?
(both)
No!
We just decided not to be
boyfriend and girlfriend
anymore.
You can't break up!
Yeah, you're just like
Ken and Barbie.
Daddy, make them hug
and say, "I love you."
Could you guys hug
and say, "I love you?"
Well, it's nice to see everyone,
but I really should get going.
Oh, Becky, I've an idea.
Why not all of us
and, I mean, all of us
go to the movies tonight?
It's on me
and the tooth fairy.
Oh, that's nice, girls.
But I have plans tonight.
- Um, I'll see you guys later.
- See ya.
I can't believe it!
She already has a date!
Becky, wait!
You and Uncle Jesse are gonna
get back together, aren't you?
Deej, I can't promise you that.
Becky, you have to.
I mean, if you'd stop
coming over..
...I'd really miss you.
Hey..
...you and I are always
gonna be friends.
You mean, we can still go riding
and talk and stuff?
Absolutely. Anytime you
need me, I'm here for you.
Thanks, Becky.
I'll tell you what,
this afternoon
you and Stephanie
and I can go see that movie.
Great! Don't forget,
it's on Stephanie.
- Got it. Later, dude.
- Later, babe.
Becky's on the way up.
- Where's Uncle Jesse?
- He's not here yet.
Then how are we gonna
get them back together?
- We gotta stall Becky.
- Got it.
Girls, you ready
for the movie?
Not yet. You gotta make up
with Uncle Jesse, first.
Good stall, Steph.
You know, Uncle Jesse
feels really terrible.
He told us how sorry
he was for everything
he's supposed
to be sorry for.
He's going around with this
sad little puppy face like..
You do the best Elvis that
I've ever seen any woman do.
- I have to be honest.
- Thanks, Jess.
I love watching
your band rehearse.
Uh, thanks, I just feel bad
that you had to listen
to "Viva Las Vegas"
seven times.
[laughing]
I loved it.
You could put out
a whole album of just that song.
- Do you think?
- Uh-huh.
You know, this is amazing.
This whole day has been great.
Becky would've never sat
through a rehearsal.
Let me ask you something,
now, if I said
"Let's hop on a Harley,
go to Vegas
roll some dice,"
what would you say?
- I'd say, "Your bike or mine?"
- Yes!
Becky would say, "Let's stay
here and play Yahtzee."
Oh, so how come you can't
go five minutes
without mentioning Becky?
Uh, did I mention Becky?
Well, you did break into
a chorus of "Viva Las Becky."
Sorry, alright, I promise,
I'm gonna go upstairs
and I won't mention
the 'B' word, okay?
I won't even say anything
that ends in "ecky".
No, no, no,
shecky, no trekky, I..
- Uncle Jesse, I've gotta--
- Not now, D.J..
- Becky's here!
- My Becky?
I mean, my ex, Becky?
And-and-and sh-she's
down there and Be..
Oh, I gotta think.
Kid, hang on.
She said she was really
sorry for everything
she's supposed
to be sorry for.
Really?
All she does is make this
sad little puppy face like..
Really?
I'm pretty sure
she stopped crying.
- Oh, she was crying?
- All day.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Well, it's nice of you
to apologize.
Yeah, well, I..
Nice of me?
D.J. said..
Oh, what's the difference
what D.J. said?
She said you made that cute
little puppy dog face like this.
Oh, no, no, no.
They said you went..
Come on, didn't you guys
miss each other
like crazy just a little?
Well, maybe I missed her
like crazy just a little..
...if she missed me.
Did you?
Of course, I missed you.
Oh, Becky, I've been thinking
about you non-stop.
Jess, I thought
we were leaving?
- Well..
- Who's this?
- Uh, well..
- You said that already.
You've anything
else to say?
No, I-I think I'd just like
to stick with "well."
This could get ugly.
Well, it's nice to meet you,
whoever you are.
I'm sure you two have
a lot in common. Goodbye, Jess.
Stay here one second.
Wait!
You couldn't
even wait one day?
I-I only made a date because
you said you made a date.
I didn't say I made a date,
I said I made plans.
- Well, a plan's a date, I--
- Excuse me,
But there's
no other way out of here.
- I'm really sorry, Diane.
- I hope you're Becky.
'Cause if you're not, you're
going to hear an awful lot
about her for the rest
of the day.
Really? You were
talking about me?
Yeah, I was talking about you,
I was thinking about..
I even sang, "Viva Las Becky."
[laughs]
Come on.
I hate it when we fight.
I mean, so silly.
First you get mad,
then I get mad.
Oh, no! That's not
the way it happens.
You always get
mad before I do.
What? I don't get mad
before you do--
[indistinct argument]
Alright, stop.
What are we fighting about
this time?
I think we're fighting
about the way we fight.
This maybe our
stupidest fight yet.
Why do we fight like this?
Nobody ever wins.
Becky, I don't wanna win, I
just...I want you to understand
me better, that's all.
Of course, if I happen
to win in the process..
Wait a minute, I think
you may have accidently
said something useful.
- I did?
- Yes!
Instead of arguing with each
other, why don't we try
really listening
to each other?
We might learn something
about the person we care about.
That's exactly
what I want.
That's, I want us to know
each other better.
Understand each other. I..
Let-let's put this into play,
alright?
Let's try this
with our problem.
Now, you don't wanna
go to the club
because it's loud, smoky,
filthy and disgusting, right?
Exactly, I couldn't have
said it better.
And you don't wanna ride horses
because they're stupid
smelly, and potentially
dangerous.
Exactly, so all we have
to do is to give up everything
we ever loved before
and we'll both be happy, right?
- Wrong!
- Good,
'Cause I just
got this new guitar
and I-I'd hate
to give it up.
Jesse, we don't have
to give up anything.
We can do our own things
and still be a couple.
- We can?
- Sure, we can.
How about if you only go riding
with me, because you want to?
Alright, alright and you
only go to the club with me
because you want to.
Okay, but never because we
feel we have to.
Alright. I gotta
tell you something.
I'm-I'm still going
horseback riding with you
because...I-I just really
love being with you.
You're so sweet.
Now, there is one good
thing about our fighting.
What's that?
We have a great time making up.
Yes, because our love
is more important
than any puddle of mud
or smoky club..
- Jess?
- Or smelly horse..
- Or flies..
- Jesse?
- Or, yeah?
Just say, "Have mercy"
and kiss me?
Have mercy!
(both)
Aww!
I knew they were
gonna come in!
Well, I just wanna thank you
girls for sticking your noses
where they don't belong.
- Anytime, Uncle Jesse.
- Let's go to the movies.
It's still my treat.
Steph, I don't think
$20 will be enough.
I'm good for it. I've got
a mouthful of baby teeth.
- Here's 20 bucks.
- Yeah.
- Here's 40.
♪ Aah aah aah aah ♪
[instrumental music]
[music continues]